I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
Answer
of the dream so quiet not giving up hope
interesting. Thanks for listening to the song. Hey, welcome and welcome in today. I'm not feeling 100%.
I bet I wanted to come deliver these horoscopes for you today. Horoscopes, they're actually
really spooky today. I mean, can I put something on the screen?
I can just leave there for the four horoscopes. Let me see. I'm gonna put up
I'll just put up a spooky background. Oh, you can't even see it. Okay, never mind. Okay.
Let's get into it. We're starting with Scorpio this year.
It's Halloween, okay? Scorpio, this year I call you the Haunted Mirror.
Prediction for Scorpio someone tries to ghost you but jokes on them you like ghosts
Prophecy for Scorpio. What you stare into will stare back, but only one of you will blink
I have a symbol for you. Just spooky symbol. It's a cracked hand may reflecting eyes that aren't yours
Okay
Let's go to Sagittarius Sagittarius
I call you the pumpkin prophet this year, so your prediction for Sagittarius is you'll accidentally join a cult again
This time they worship pumpkin spice
Prophecy this fire you start for warmth may roast your own marshmallows
Watch out for that spooky symbol for Sagittarius a jack-o-lantern grinning with too many teeth
Okay
What do you call a jack-o-lantern that needs to go to the dentist?
I don't know.
Can someone come up with a good punchline for that?
Okay, so Capricorn is next.
Capricorn, and these are quick.
And I'll just tell you how long I say it.
Capricorn, you're known as the graveyard CEO.
Protection for Capricorn.
You'll sign a business deal with a vampire.
He offers eternal youth in the fine print.
A prophecy for Capricorn.
What you build in stone will whisper in bone.
A spooky symbol for Capricorn.
I'm a Capricorn.
A golden coin have melted into a skull.
Okay, just that image may trigger something. Okay. Next, we have the Aquarius, the Aquarius, the mad scientist, the Dr. Frankenstein of the chat, not Frankenstein the monster, the Dr. Frankenstein, the actual Frankenstein. Okay.
So prediction for Aquarius, you'll invent a potion that brings your phone battery back to life, but also your ex.
Okay, the prophecy for you this season, innovation without empathy, births to monsters that look like mirrors.
Spooky symbol a lightning bolt trapped in a mason jar
Think about that one. Okay next week. We have about Pisces. I call Pisces the dream droner
Pisces is all about dreaming but also been a lot of water. Where are those water dreams?
with a water look.
So prediction for Pisces,
this year you'll actually project it to someone's nightmare
and accidentally fix their trauma.
Okay, prophecy, the tide returns every secret,
even the ones you're staying to sleep.
And your spooky symbol for this year,
Pisces is a seashell filled with whispers instead of ocean.
Listen to the seashell.
Okay, next we have Aries.
Aries, I'll call the curse to dear devil.
Areas are baby of the zodiac. You'll run ahead first into danger and win, but with new horns
Okay, run near the bulls prophecy the flame that leaps first
learns which shadows bite
Spooky symbol for areas of burning match that laughs instead of fizzes
Okay, next we have Taurus the possessed foodie
Taurus you'll eat something just to try it and end up hosting a minor demon named Carl
Okay, watch out. So comfort is a curse when it hums your name too sweetly. And your spooky symbol for the year is a silver fork that reflects fangs instead of your face.
Ooh, spooky. Okay, Gemini, you ready? Gemini, the doppelganger. Again, the doppelganger twin.
So my prediction this year is you'll meet your twin, they'll steal your punchlines and your door dash order. Okay, your prophecy is two mouths, one spell, only silence saves the soul.
Mm-hmm spooky symbol a mirror cracked perfectly down the middle
Okay, next we have cancer I cook cancer the seance chef, you know cancers are great great cooks
My mom is a cancer
fabulous cook
Prediction for cancer you'll make cupcakes for the dead, okay
they'll leave five-star reviews in blood your prophecy this year is the love you
feed will always return hungry and a spooky symbol for you a whisk stirring
on its own Leo the haunted spotlight
Right, we know Leo's love that spotlight prediction for Leo's you'll post a selfie so powerful it resurrects your haters
Your prophecy for Leo is the crown burns the brightest on those who dare dance in their ashes
Your spooky symbol is a lion's shadow wearing your face
Okay, and we have a few more signs to go
We're enjoying ourselves
You're on poem with the static bar or state bar. Okay
Please not too much of a
a nightmare call. Okay, so we do have Virgo and Libra left and we'll have the full horoscopes
for everybody. Bear with me for one second. Hi Jay, how are you? Okay. So Virgo and Libra,
So Virgo, you are known as the perfection of poltergeist
The prediction for you is you'll reorganize your bookshelf and accidentally alphabetize the ghosts of unfinished business
Proposy order is the illusion that lures chaos closer. Oh my gosh. It's spooky symbol for you a
Quill writing list after midnight though your pen is capped
Finally, we have Libra. I'm going to call Libra the bewitched matchmaker prediction for Libra
You'll mediate a breakup between two spirits. They'll both end up dating you
Oh Libra a prophecy for Libra balance teeters on the blade of desire and you always find the edge
Okay, spooky symbol a set of scales way down by rose petals and bones. Okay
Well, take what you wish out of these horoscopes.
OK, I'm going to offer a few things.
I'm going to offer my astrological reports.
I'll give you a full astrological report, including music.
It will include at least three images.
This is my normal $50 report, I will do for $25, I will have it done in 24 hours, cash
app, dollar sign, Psyche Awakens, you can also find my PayPal link in my description, private
I will do $25.30 minutes on the phone or by video call.
Again, catch up, Psyche Awakens,
I'll contact you within a few hours
and we'll have the reading scheduled
within the next 24 hours, okay?
And that's what I have for you right now, okay?
I'm a little bit
Krabby
Okay, I'm a little bit my cancer energy my Krabby energy
little stressed out but
Guys, um, let's let's all um
Help each other. Do you know help out the cult? I do have more cult emojis and stuff like that
I'm not gonna keep you waiting too long. There's I guess, you know, there's a lot of people dropped off the show
you know
And I watched I watched um, you know who's
rerun last night and you know for the person that says oh I
Don't talk, you know, don't talk about me. They sure talk about me a lot. Sure. My name is sure brought up a lot a
lot
But I will still refrain from talking about them, but
You know for someone that says never contact me again, you know
You're bothering me. She they sure do address me a lot. Hey Nancy. How are you?
Anyone has any questions video wants a card before I go. I'm just like, you know
No, I don't have to back go practically
Sitting feeling
Yeah, I know I know because it's like oh, you know, she's not talking but she's doing other stuff and it's like
It just feels like I'm being roasted the entire time.
Oh, making fun of people that use AI,
making fun of people that do music.
I mean, it's like, everything that I do
is like, criticizable.
And she's just like, that's perfect, but anyway.
Oh, thank you, Jamie. I'm going to use those. You need to rewind?
Ah, nothing much happened. I mean, it's like, you know, I just, you know, unrumble. They replay episodes.
Her whole stream was a subliminal mock at me. I know. I know.
Like, I mean, I almost want to show you I can play. I mean, because I was like, oh, it's going to be
subliminal. But then it was like, they should have just been talking about me or using my name.
I mean, I'm not I don't even bother watching the whole thing because it's like it's just too much
Yeah, the north of Halloween. Are you here tricks?
The guy that you can't help me out this Halloween, you know, it always gets a little a little
Difficult around Halloween if you would like to purchase one of the reports it will not only help you out. It'll help me out
I will be in a better mood
Okay, but maybe I'll go check out that subliminal stream and just see exactly
What messages are trying to be sent to me, right?
Yeah, even time and sweet peace time time my mod my mod is time
He hopped on panel talking about okay, so I need to go see that
And you go see that I'll play one more song and then I'll
I'll let you guys go. I love you guys. So thank you so much for being here. I'll be back later. I'll try to be
Appreciate if anyone